AHMED MOAHMMED OBAD

ahmd4obad@gmail.com 735222168 12, 24 st Haddah, Sana'a

Summary

Top-performing Project Manager with +5 years of experience in directing operations, motivating staff, and identifying business growth opportunities. With Information Technology background, I am a web application developer with +3 years of experience in web Designs & developing

Experience

Web Developer/Programmer (Remotely)

Creative Unicorn Agency • Subang, Selengor 03/2021 - Present

- Partner with clients to develop strategies and help translate their functional/business requirements into web-based solutions that support the unit's overall mission and vision.
- Create, edit, manage, and maintain web sites and/or applications that support unit initiatives.
- Establish workflow and service agreements in order to analyze priorities and problems and evaluate their impact on services and timelines.
- Develop web standards and guidelines for style, content and code through 1) research of current web trends, 2) usability testing of clients, 3) surveys of clients and content managers, 4) administrative
- feedback and benchmarks, 5) university computer use policies and 6) relevant laws (e.g. 508 compliance and copyright).
- Establish and maintain effective working relationships between IT and client communities; identify new and ongoing client needs.
- Monitor and analyze web-related statistics; identify trends in the nature, frequency, and types of services requested, and use this data to continually improve content and quality of services.
- Implement appropriate security measures to safeguard data and restrict access appropriately.
- Audit web sites and applications to ensure that standards are met; security measures are in place and determine and address the impact of new requirements and programming changes required.

Web Developer/Programmer (Part-time)

Kaff Media • Haddah, Sana'a 01/2021 - Present

Handling the NOGs projects for Kaff Media

- · Write well designed, testable, efficient code by using best software development practices
- · Create website layout/user interface by using standard HTML/CSS, Jquiry, React.js practices
- Integrate data from various back-end services and databases
- Gather and refine specifications and requirements based on technical needs
- · Create and maintain software documentation

- · Be responsible for maintaining, expanding, and scaling our site
- · Stay plugged into emerging technologies/industry trends and apply them into operations and activities
- · Cooperate with web designers to match visual design intent

Web Developer/Programmer

Ecompile.io • PJ, Selangor 03/2020 - 03/2021

Web Developer as Programmer and front-end designer

Administrative Assistance

RNW Media • Sana'a, Sana'a 01/2015 - 02/2017

Responsible of collecting the data recorded on the data collection forms is entered onto the database completely and accurately within time limits, Compiling, verifying accuracy and sorting the data, Reviewing the data for Null values, Maintaining the project documents, Appling functions to excel to generate reports and improving the database, generate reports and charts, design and maintain the database using Excel or Microsoft Azure, Editing, cleaning, updating, and compiling periodically received data or errors for RNW origination based in Sana'a Yemen

Manager Assistant & Information Management admin

Global Gide Travels (Malaysia) • Bukit Bintang, Kuala Lumpur 11/2017 - 02/2020

I was responsible of arranging the necessarily documents of hotels air flights, staff files, Arranging meetings for internal or with external companies, communicate with clients, Hotels, Airways companies or any government department to collect data or make any deal. I also had to organize the tours plans for the drivers. I had created the company website and I was the admin of the website during my work period.

Web Developer

YemenSoft • Sana'a, Haddah 11/2013 - 03/2014

atteneded a trining programme in YemenSoft yemen, I have completed one internal web application project.

Seller

Al-Mazen • Sana'a, Haddah 01/2010 - 11/2011

I was responsible of the laptops section

Skills

- ability to work co-operatively with others
 Experience of working with confidential
- Experience in writing the reports
- MySQL, Postgres DB, MongoDB
- CSS
- Jquery
- WordPress
- GitHub
- Git
- REACT.JS, React Native

- Experience of working with confidential data
- Abode XD, Illustrator, Photoshop, Phone Gap
- HTML
- JavaScript
- Bootstrap
- PHP, Laravel
- Databases
- Web flow
- ReactJS

- · NODE.JS
- · React Native
- Excel
- EMR
- Scheduling
- Project Management
- Collaboration
- Creativity
- · Problem solving
- Adaptability

- Sales
- Excellent in using Microsoft Excel, word and Outlook
- Powerpoint
- Management
- · Microsoft office
- · Leadership Experience
- Communications
- · Critical thinking
- · Visual thinking
- Customer service
- · Experience of working in a fast-paced office environment

Education

Information & Communication Technology

LUCT • Cyberjaya, Selangor 12/2014

Foundation In Communication Engineering

Sana'a University • Sana'a, Sana'a 01/2010

English

Exceed language Center • Sana'a, Sana'a 01/2009

Completed a course in English language, the Advanced level (GRAD CF).

Languages

English

Arabic

Reference

Reference available upon request

Links

My Website/ Portfolio

<u>LinkedIn</u>